[ED.
Well Sauce and Saegusa
Well-suited and mandarin oranges
Hot.
Really great
I can't get enough of this humidity.
I'm a woman who loves summer, so I can't get enough of it!
It's so hot!
But I hear it's even hotter!
I hear it's even hotter.
I hear the temperature goes up even higher during the day!
Convenience store in Thailand
Convenience stores in Thailand
Yes, there are a lot of them!
There's even one that tastes like "Yama Yama Kun"!
Mr. Curry, here it is!
Haguki!
Haguki
Natural Haguki
Kaya-san
This is Ms. Kaya
My boyfriend.
Seriously?
I was going for him.
Oh, shit.
What should I buy?
Oh, Dekamizu.
I'll get one too.
I'll buy a big bottle of water
I'll buy a big bottle of water.
I have a big bottle of water.
Do you have any good ones?
Something tasty.
Oh, hey, something chocolatey.
We can go to a convenience store.
This looks good.
It's so cute.
Looks good.
It doesn't look good.
It's not expensive.
I tried to put this on the table.
It's 800 yen.
That's because it's really Japanese.
Look at this.
Japanese sweets can be expensive
Japanese sweets are expensive.
I want some.
It's Rine's fault.
Oh, sorry
Pumpkin loin
Wow!
What is this?
Plums.
Twenty.
Only 2 for 8.
You're a challenger, aren't you?
Challenger.
Mango.
Something about... getting me a coconut candy bar.
Coconut candy.
Coconut candy?
I'm not buying it.
My mom wants me to buy coconut candy.
Coconut candy.
I don't think so.
She said to buy lots of coconut candy.
She told you to buy a lot of coconut candy.
She told you to buy a lot of coconut candy?
This looks delicious.
Jesus.
This is the venue for today's concert.
Ta-da!
I thought the unit was incredibly hot, and it was hot, but I was able to go until I was sweating, so it's like a nice summer.
Good morning.
About 2 minutes to go. Let's dance already.
Bye.
I'm going home.
Pun-pun.
As we are playing together today.
For our guests to have fun.
I hope everyone gets a hoodie.
I'm going to do my best
With two customers today
The end was a lot of fun
Let's continue with the next tray
Pop-pop-pop
Pop, pop, pop, pop
Did you all ride?
Did you ride together?
Introduce yourself one by one.
Are you in love right now?
Okay, one at a time.
I'm in love with you all.
Idols 100%.
I'm in love with Tork, the staff, and everyone.
I love you all, but I'm not in love with you.
My favorite fish is love.
Good luck, Rio-kun!
Next
Kaya-san, it'll be over in 3 seconds
I want to ride on you
I want to ride Dosan, too.
We all said we'd buy dai-pan before we went together
I'm saying...
I don't know where they're sold.
I want to know where people are buying them
Where we did it today.
They were on sale.
Maybe a shopping mall.
We'd all like to buy matching ones there.
And that's something I'd like to do.
I also wanted to take a lot of pictures.
I want to take a lot of pictures.
Thank you very much for your hard work!
I'm having fun!
I'm so happy!
John Chi?
Moooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo!
Oh, my gosh!